[SOUND] In last week's module we learned about different visualization systems,
[音乐]上周我们学习了 不同的可视化系统
how computer graphics is used to present data,
计算机图形学如何呈现数据
and most importantly how we observe data and
以及更重要的 我们如何观察数据
perceive the data based on how it's presented.
如何根据数据的呈现方式 来认知数据
In this week's module, we'll be focusing on the data and
本周 我们将关注数据
different attributes of the data and how best to
以及数据的不同属性
incorporate that into a visualization system for its effective display.
以及如何把这些属性包含进 可视化系统 使其能有效地显示
Here's an example using Tableau, which is one of several different
这是一个使用Tableau的例子 Tableau是现有的帮助将数据可视化
visualization systems that are available to help with visualizing data.
的不同可视化系统其中之一
We have data on the left.
我们的数据在左侧
And the is the data from the World Bank Indicators.
是从世界银行指数 获得的数据
And, for example, we might be interested in life expectancy.
比如说 我们也许对 预期寿命感兴趣
And we might also want to see,
我们也许还想看看
how does infant mortality affect the estimate of life expectancy?
新生儿死亡率如何影响 预期寿命的估算
And then we might want to separate that by country or region.
然后我们还想按国家 或地区把数据分开
So Tableau, for example, has this Show Me button here in the upper right corner.
在Tableau的右上角 有一个Show Me按钮
The Show Me button, you can click that, and
你可以点击这个Show Me按钮
based on the data you've selected, Tableau
根据你选择的数据
will show you the specific kinds of charts you may want to use to display that data.
Tableau会显示你可能想用的 特定种类的图表
We click on one of those, and we automatically get a visualization of that
点击其中的一个 就自动得到了一个可视化
data, where the, horizontally the columns are showing infant mortality.
每列横坐标显示新生儿死亡率
Vertically, the rows are showing us the average life expectancy.
每行纵坐标显示平均预期寿命
So, as we move vertically up, we're seeing life expectancy.
沿纵轴向上 我们看到预期寿命
Horizontally, we're seeing infant mortality.
沿横轴 我们看到新生儿死亡率
And then each one of these circles is indicating a different
这里每一个圆圈
country that we might be looking at.
表示一个不同的国家
And so, if you use Tableau you can use this Show Me
所以 如果你用Tableau 你可以用这个Show Me屏
screen in order to automatically find the appropriate kinds of visualization methods
来自动选择合适的可视化方法
you would use for that.
你将会这么用
What I'm going to be talking about this week and actually in module four
本周 以及第四周 我们将谈谈
in the fourth week of the class is the background information.
关于可视化的一些背景信息
The papers that have been written on the subject
和围绕这个主题的一些论文
that went in to creating this Show Me button so that we can figure out how this
其中的构想被引入这个Show Me 功能的设计中 我们才能搞明白
Show Me button automatically laid out this data in the appropriate manner.
Show Me按钮是如何以恰当方式 来自动安排可视化的
So that you can use any tool you like to set up your visualizations.
让你可使用任何你喜欢的工具 来配置你的可视化
There's obviously other reasons you would want to use Tableau, but
很明显 使用Tableau还有其他原因
you'll know enough to be able to do the same thing that the Show Me button is
但你将会了解的 将使你能够在任何可视化系统
doing on your own with any visualization system.
完成与Show Me按钮同样的功能
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community